We also have settings. So setting is about the aspect ratio of the
Result image as well as the resolution
So you can either be standard or high quality. You can see the sizing over here
We also have a number of images that it is it is going to generate us
So as you see if I change it to one it will now
demand one and you know eliminate one of my credits, you know, it will take one credit for one image
But if I say two it will take two credits if I say four it'll take four credits as you see, right?
So I come back to one. I say I just want a single image out of it and visibility
It can either be public or private the private edition casts you something so it's on the promo right and we also have
Negative prompts. We can turn it on
What do you want to avoid you know, so
This is also cool. For example, you want this image, but you're very very
Specific about some other things that you do not want so this is your prompt and in this settings
You'll be able to add some negative prompts over here
The things that you want to avoid and the things you do not want to have in the generated result
Yes, I turn it off. I don't have any for now